

PROFILE

With a passion for people and a love for the security industry I hope to be a great addition to your team. To continue expanding the variety of my experience and knowledge in the pursuit of an Information Systems Security career, I intend to amass a variety of knowledge from each corner of the security industry. In these first steps out of post secondary school I hope to commit myself to a team that values space for education and growth. With the belief in my hard work, ingenuity, and moldability in a team environment I believe I would make a great addition to any workforce.

CONTACT

Phone:

403-809-3342

Email:

alexgmyth@outlook.com

SKILLS

- Strong leadership skills
- Conflict resolution
- Strong work ethic
- Exceptional communicator
- Efficient time management

ALEX SMITH

GRADUATE OF THE SOUTHERN ALBERTA INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY WITH A DIPLOMA IN INFORMATION SYSTEMS SECURITY

EDUCATION

Southern Alberta Institute of Technology (SAIT)

2019 - 2021

Graduated April 2021 from the Information Systems Security program

EDUCATIONAL COURSES:

- Networking Protocols and Security
- Military and Strategic Studies
- Secure Programming Essentials
- Advanced Networking for Offensive/Defensive Environments
- Reverse Engineering of IOT devices
- Wireless Security
- Operating System Exploitation
- Malware Analysis
- Web Application Security
- Security Policies and Operations
- PCI Compliance and Encryption
- Computer Forensics
- Social Engineering
- Capstone Projects

Crescent Heights High School

2015 - 2018

Graduated June 2018

- Strong problem-solving ability
- Works well in interdisciplinary teams
- Accountable
- Ability to work in a fast-paced environment
- Follows policies, processes, and directions
- Strong organization skills
- Motivated learner
- Co-Curricular Peer Mentor through SAIT
- Team captain for ACVC Volleyball Club 18U 2016-2018
- Taekwondo Black Stripe

WORK EXPERIENCE

Telus - Koodo Mobile Crossiron Mills - Sales Representative (Part time - 2021-present)

- Being part of a collaborative effort to rank second place in Alberta for sales value.
- Primarily focusing on customer experiences and strategically creating sales opportunities.
- Working with diverse populations with limited tech experience, to make cellular technology understandable and enjoyable.
- Contrary to the popular sales technique I prioritize creating a nurturing and unique customer service relationship.

VOR - Pentesting Android Applications (Casual - July - August 2021)

Hired pentester for the B-Line android app

- First hand experience white-box pentesting the B-Line android app.
- Used social engineering to find usernames and passwords for app logins.
- Performed several known exploits concerned with character sanitization.
- Analyzed the android app's manifest file to expose severe issues

Telus - Public Mobile Marlborough Mall - Sales Representative (Part Time - February-September 2020)

Chasing Summer Festival - Bartender Associate (Casual - August 2019)

Proserve certified

Volcom Market Mall - Sales Associate (Part Time June 2016-March 2019)

Team Lead March 2019 - March 2019

Training:

• Educated in C++, Python, JavaScript

References

- 1. Paul Smith VOR Owner 4038701753
- 2. Andi North Personal Reference 4038500704
- Owen Almquist Koodo Coworker and Team Lead -5872204796